？
Hello and welcome to real easyy English, the podcast where we have real conversations in easy English to help you learn I'm Georgie and I'm Neil to watch a video
version of this podcast and download a free worksheet go to our websitelearningenglish.
com.
The.
Hi Neil how are you Are you happy to be at work today Of course I'm always happy to be at work Great well today we are talking about dream jobs obviously this
job is amazing but we're going to talk about some different jobs we'd like to do sounds good Sha we start Yes So Georgie when you were a child what
did you want to do when you grew up what was your dream job Well when I was really little?
About five or six, I remember telling people that I wanted to be a princess when I realized that wasn't going to be possible for me,
my next dream was to be a pop star because, My friends and I used to write songs and perform in front of our parents and I thought that would be really
fun Yeah what about you Well kind of similar.
I think actually when I was when I was a child, I thought that being a professional sportsman would be fantastic either a footballer or
a cricketer what went wrong I'm not good enough?
I learned that lesson, but also I wanted when I got a little bit older sort of teenage and started playing guitar,
I thought, yeah, maybe a rock star would be the thing for me.
So Neil, obviously you are not a rock star, but how or when did you decide to become an English teacher instead?
Well, when I finished university I wanted to travel more than anything else and I wanted to live in foreign countries not just go on holiday and I thought a good
way to do that would be to become an English teacher I have a similar story it was the same thing for I just wanted to live abroadorgie what is important to you about
your job now Well many of us spend a lot of our lives working so for me it's really.
Important to enjoy the day we work nine to five it's a lot of hours in the day it's really important to me to have a nice team that you can
have fun with it's also really important for me to feel like I'm giving something good or doing a good job
What about you Yeah I think it's important to feel that you're doing something useful.
.
So hopefully our conversations like this are useful for people because they can learn something and I like that Yeah me too so Neil,
if you didn't have to worry about money or anything else what would your dream job be I think I know the answer already Yeah well you said earlier that
I didn't become a rock star but there is still a future and you know, if I didn't have to work I could just.
。
Follow my dream How about you I think if I didn't do this job I would like to be a travel
photographer or someone that makes documentaries I really love those nature documentaries and it would be very fun to be involved in those Yes that
sounds like it would be amazing.
The.
Okay let's recap the language we heard during the conversation we can describe something like a job as important to us for example I said that a nice team at work is
important to me we talked about our dream jobs when we were children using the structure when I was younger I wanted to be So for example when I was
younger I wanted to be a footballer and we talked about our dream jobs now using conditionals so for example.
If I could do any job I would be a travel photographer and when we're talking about jobs we can do them or we can be them for example I
teach English or I am an English teacher and that's it for this episode of real easy English if you like our programs why not sign up to our email you can get
suggestions for other English lessons you might enjoy there's a in the notes for this program us again.